http://qmi-scotland.co.uk/privacy-statement/

Home > Privacy Statement
QMI Scotland Limited is committed to protecting your privacy. When you browse through our web site, we collect information on the efficiency and working of our web site. This information includes the number of times a web page is accessed, the browser used, and paths taken when moving through the web site.
Collecting your Personal Information
QMI Scotland Limited will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are asked to register before requesting e-mail newsletters or providing feedback.
Use of your Personal Information
QMI Scotland Limited uses your personal information for the following primary purposes:
To make the web site easier for you to use by asking you to enter your personal information only once.
To provide on-line services
To help us create and deliver content most relevant to you.
QMI Scotland Limited does not share this information with any other organisation.
QMI Scotland Limited will not disclose your personal information, without notice, and then, only if required to do so by law.
Use of Cookies
To ensure this web site meets our visitors’ needs QMI Scotland Limited collects web site statistics using cookies.
When someone visits one of our web sites, a cookie is placed on the visitor’s machine (if the customer accepts cookies) or is read if the customer has visited the site previously.
Changes to this Statement
QMI Scotland Limited may occasionally update this privacy statement. When this is done we will also revise the ‘last updated’ date of the privacy statement.
Contact Information
QMI Scotland Limited welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. QMI Scotland Limited can be easily contacted (see Contact Us page).
© Website copyright 2020, QMI Scotland limited.
Company number 2526956.
Registered office: Suite 1, 3rd Floor, 11-12 St. James’s Square, London, SW1Y 4LB
Web design in Aberdeen
